Are you kidding me?
Joey?
Did I wake you?
The One with
All the Wedding Dresses
Gunther, could I get
another cup of coffee?
So what do you do when
you're not working here?
-You don't need to fill these silences.
-Okay, thanks.
That's your fourth cup of coffee.
Okay, do me.
I've had a certain number of juices.
I'm exhausted because
Joey started snoring.
He's in a different room.
He's that loud?
You should hear me.
It's nothing to be proud of.
Go to a sleep clinic.
I'm not going to any clinic.
I don't have a problem.
You have the problem.
You should go to a "Quit-being-
a-baby-and-leave-me-alone" clinic.
-They don't have those.
-Yeah, they do.
Quit being a baby and leave me alone!
There, you just had your first class.
I used to date a light sleeper.
Whenever I snored,
he rolled me over
Oh, yeah!
He'd roll me over,
and I'd stop snoring.
Next time you snore,
I'm rolling you over!
I gotta do what I gotta do.
You gotta do what you gotta do.
Hey, guys.
Oh, the Olympics!
-Have you picked a date?
-No. Not yet.
I still cannot believe
you're engaged.
Because it's so fast.
Not because you're a loser.
Thanks. Has anyone seen Rach?
She's upstairs not doing the dishes.
I won't do them this time.
Even if they sit there until....
I'll do them when I get home.
Emily found this
wedding dress in London
-Already?
-But it didn't fit.
There's a store here with one left in her size.
But the groom can't see
-I'll pick it up for you.
-Thanks.
She's got you running errands,
picking up wedding dresses....
Wah-pah!
What's wah-pah?
You know. Whipped.
Wah-pah!
That's not whipped.
Whipped is....
That's what I did.
You can't do anything!
Hey, Mon.
I was just doing these dishes.
Do you have a minute?
I was just about to
take a break anyway.
So listen...
...I know we haven't had
a chance to talk...
...since Emily and l
decided to get married.
And I was just wondering
how you were.
If you were getting married,
I would feel kind of....
You know?
It definitely took me by surprise.
But, you know...
...I'm okay.
I just wanted to check.
That's sweet. Thank you.
You're great.
And I know someday this will
happen for you too.
You just hang in there.
"Hang in there"?
No, I didn't mean....
You haven't heard of a serious
relationship called "me and Joshua"?
I thought you had
just been on four dates.
I didn't realize that had
become anything.
Oh no, it has become.
Oh no, those were four great dates.
I mean, and the connection!
Emotionally, mentally.
You know?
Physically.
-That's incredible.
-I know, isn't it?
I'm right there with Joshua.
You are right there with Emily.
And it's kind of like it's a tie.
I gotta get back to my dishes.
I gotta get to work.
You know what would
make me happy?
You know, what's that?
If the four of us could all,
you know, hang out together.
Emily's coming into
town this weekend.
Why don't we all
have dinner Sunday night?
That would be great!
All right. It's a date!
"Hang in there."
You hang in there.
-Did you say something?
-No, just singing.
Oh, my God!
Look at this one!
It's so beautiful.
About half of these will
end up getting divorced.
May I help you ladies?
I'm here to pick up a dress on hold.
What's the name?
-Emily Waltham.
-Yes, I have it right here.
Would you like to try it on,
Miss Waltham?
You're the most beautiful bride
I've ever seen.
I am, aren't l?
Miss Waltham?
We're closing.
All right.
And could I get my ring back?
All right, buddy.
Time to roll over.
You are going to a clinic!
You're going to a clinic!
And a pajama store!
Does she use the cups?
Yes, I believe she does.
Does she use the plates?
Yes, I believe she does!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming.
-Just a second.
-No, no! Let me in!
Can you hold on a minute?
No! You have to
let me in right now!
Are you alone?
All right.
This sucks.
I have to stay up all night
before I go to the stupid clinic.
I'm so tired.
It's six o'clock.
I hear you and Joshua are
going out with Ross and Emily.
I think that's really cool.
I think you're handling
that really well.
"Handling it"?
There's nothing to handle.
Maybe I'd have a problem with this
if it wasn't for me and Joshua.
They're not going to
get married anyway.
They rushed into this thing
so fast, it's ridiculous!
They'll be engaged for like what?
A year?
One of them will realize
what they've done...
...and call it off.
You'll be dancing at my wedding
before you dance at theirs.
You know, I don't dance at weddings.
Why not?
Weddings are a great place
to meet women.
When I dance, I look like this.
Hey, man.
What are you doing
four weeks from today?
-Nothing.
I am...
...free.
Because we're getting
married in a month.
-What?
-Yes.
In a month?
-You mean 30 days?
-Yeah.
From now?
That's great!
She always wanted to get married
where her parents did...
...but it's getting torn down.
I know it's crazy,
but everything's been so crazy...
...and it just feels right.
Hey, that's the day after
I start menstruating!
This isn't mine.
-Hey, Rachel.
-Hi.
What's up?
Your voice sounded
all squeaky on the phone.
Nothing.
I just wanted to see you.
See you and hug you.
See you....
Great!
Sit.
You okay?
I'm more than okay.
I am really, really happy.
Want to know why?
Do l?
Because I am really happy about us.
I think we are so
on the right track.
I think we are working.
I think we are clicking.
-You know?
-Yeah, sure, sure.
We're clicking.
If there was just
one little area where...
...I think we need to work on,
I would think...
...it's that we're
just not crazy enough.
I got to say, I'm not too sure
I agree with that.
You know, yeah, you're right.
We have our fun. Yeah?
I mean, like crazy!
You know?
Are you gonna put on
that cheerleader outfit again?
No. You wish.
All right.
This is going to sound, you know,
a little hasty.
But just go with me.
What if we got married?
-What?
-Oh, I know. It's so totally like...
..."Whoa, can we do this?"
You know?
But it just feels right.
Don't you think it does?
I mean, it just feels right.
Don't you...?
Rachel...
...you're...
...a real...
...special lady.
But my divorce isn't final yet...
...and we've been on four dates.
So I'm thinking: No...
...but...
...thanks.
You idiot!
-Your name, please?
-Joey Tribbiani.
Did you stay up all night
in preparation for your study?
Sir?
Yes, he did.
All right. We'll call you
in a few minutes.
Check out that girl.
She's really hot.
Yeah, she is.
How you doing?
You looking good.
-What?
-You're coming on to the entire room.
-I'm Chandler.
-I'm Marjorie.
-Do you mind if I sit?
-Please.
So what are you in for?
I talk in my sleep.
What a coincidence!
I listen in my sleep.
So why don't you give me your number?
Are you ready?
I got it! Mine!
-Congratulations!
-Thank you!
My turn, my turn!
Okay, ready?
That was a terrible throw!
I won't throw it right to you.
That's not real.
Look at me. My big concern
is what's real?
Oh, my God!
We're really sad, aren't we?
Yeah, I think we are.
This isn't even my dress.
At least you didn't rent yours from
a store called "It's Not Too Late."
-I'm changing out of this.
-Me, too.
In half an hour?
Me, too.
All right, now throw it
straight this time.
I'm getting married!
I hate my regular clothes now.
I look down and I know...
...this won't be the most
special day of my life.
I mean, it was kind of
fun for a while...
...but didn't you feel kind of silly?
I guess.
Oh, my God!
You're such a cheater!
Hello, little ones.
-So, is Joey going to stop snoring?
-Yep!
And a beautiful woman
agreed to go out with me.
Joey wanted to ask her out,
but, you know, she picked me.
How'd that happen?
Because I'm cooler.
No, seriously.
She's the kind of girl....
Joey was unconscious.
Hey, you guys!
What's happening?
Oh, my God!
What is that?
They gave it to me
at the sleep clinic...
...and it's going to help me
not to snore.
Well, are you asleep right now, Joe?
You don't have to
wear it unless you are.
I know I don't have to.
It tastes good.
Plus, you look cool.
Hope I didn't stretch Emily's dress.
Your butt's not
that much bigger than her's.
I just called Joshua.
How'd it go?
I did my best to
convince him that I'm not...
...some crazy girl who's
dying to get married.
And I'm going through
a hard time.
What'd he say?
His answering machine
was very understanding.
I feel blue.
I bet you anything
he'll call you again.
Yeah, maybe. But, you know,
I don't think I even care.
I don't think he's
the one I'm sad about.
I know I said I'm totally okay
with Ross getting married.
But as it turns out...
...I don't think I'm handling it
all that well.
Yeah, maybe.
And I'm just trying to
figure out why.
Any luck?
You know how Ross and I have
always been on-again, off-again?
I guess I just figured,
somewhere down the road...
...we would be on again.
Again.
You know what?
I think we all did.
I got us reservations
for Sunday night.
How about Ernie's at 9:00?
Well, you'd better make it for three.
I don't know if we're
going to be hungry at three.
Three people.
Joshua's not going to be there.
What happened?
Well, I think he broke up with me.
No. Why?
Apparently, he scares easy.
Rachel, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Sometimes things don't work out
the way you thought they would.
Come here.
Don't you have to go pick up Emily?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. I got my girls.
Hey, you know what might
cheer you up?
What?
I got to tell you...
...this really does put me
in a better mood.
I wish there was a job where
I could wear this all the time.
Maybe someday there will be.
Chandler's coming by to borrow
candles for his big date.
Rachel, don't get it!
He'll see us!
The groom cannot see the bride.
I'm not going to marry Chandler.
Not after this!
Okay guys, just relax.
I do!
I got to go.
Yeah, well, that ought to do it.
Food's here. Fair enough.
Fifteen-minute warning.
Late.
Dude, I am trying to sleep!